[Music]
Hello my friends,
welcome to my
Punch. It's been a year since my Punch was issued
and my insurance has
expired. I
first had Kotak for insurance, after that I had
ICICI
Hero Depot, and the third one was a Smartphone.
I bought that
and along with the policy, I got a
telematic device from ICICI Lombard, which is called tallymatic.
Now, they have given it to me after installing it,
but let me
show you its box.
This telematic is of
this type.
I will also show you what is in it,
download
drive. Now,
I will tell you what benefits we get from it. I have
also
got a GPS tracker in it and this is the Android device which connects to the Android device.
I have to download an app from the user manual.
After downloading this app, it starts working.
And this is what
I got when I got
insurance from ICICI Lombard.
Now, whose box is this?  But
where is the device actually, I will
show you the device, this is the device, this is the
device that I took out
and ours is here, it is
given by them,
you must be seeing
this object, I actually
took this male female connector because
after putting it on, my thing here was not turning off,
so this is it and
this is a GPS tracker, now
in this GPS tracker, I will open its app and
tell you what all we have got in it,
friends, this is my device and this is the
app of the device, I will tell you this app, it is
ILS which I have to insure
and in this my location and all the details are there, it is shown
here, it is
telling me my error, if there is any error in
my car, then it is
telling me the total details, like it will be live,
my life location will be automatically done,
roadside assistant, whenever I
need, then my complete details of these sources will be there,
inside it there are digital documents, I
can upload my question documents in documents whenever I need.  This will be the trip, there
will be activity, there will be driving summary and
service history too.
We can find out the trends by installing it in it.
There is a chart in trends and like the analytical report,
in the analytical report, how
we have driven the car, all of that is
generated in it, like in this, this is
my one day's report and my
score
or everything that happens is that I have
driven at driving speed, so it tells us totally
with location.
Now the
rest of it is helpful in this, now there is one thing in it, in this
alert, if
we have turned on the ignition of the car,
then it will alert us whether the ignition of the car is
on or off, it will
tell us both. Now how do we configure it in this, to
configure it,
we have to configure it in the settings, there is
alerts in the settings, in the alerts,
we have to configure it,
like engine errors, if there is any engine
error, check engine light or anything,
if anything is coming, it will tell us
if the speed is reached, till what time we have to maintain the speed,
that will be shown to us in it and
like in this we have to configure
how much speed  Till then we have to keep it in it like it is
running above 82, now put a device in it,
if we remove the device then it will
also tell us that this
device is out, if Nation On
ever gives us an alert then it will also give an alert, it will
also give an alert,
what happens many times is that we have
friends like us or someone else like
friends, it happens with our own
relatives that even if we don't want to, we have to
give the car to them, it will
come at a very low rate on time, how will it come at a low rate, like if I
told someone that I am
going up to 10 kilometers, then I have chosen
my area in Jio Fans up to
10 kilometers,
like in this we can increase or decrease it
as much as possible, now what will happen in it is that
if it goes more than that then
we will get to know that this car is
running too much, if we are taking it more than 10 kilometers then
a message will drop to us, if we are
doing hard braking then it will
also alert us, if the
document expires then our
insurance will do it
and battery  If it tells
us how much voltage is there in our battery, it is
inside this thing and this is a very
good device that
will track us, so
friends, today I just wanted to tell you
that the insurance that I had taken was due to
this inch, how is the working of the device that I got,
friends, bye bye,
if you like my video, then
please like, share and subscribe, thank you, bye bye
and take care.